

Profile



As a recent graduate, I've been working with code and development software for the last 3 years, learning anything from 2D platformer games to website structure. My favorite things are website design, and video game development. I want to create work that will inspire others, as I've been inspired.

Education &



Wilkes University

2021

BA in Digital Design and Media Art Game and Emergent Technology minor GPA: 3.6

Work Experience

Web Developer Internship

OneBuilder

Working on maintaining and updating existing websites, developing new websites, and resolving bugs using JS, Gatsby, and ReactJS.

Computer Science Tutor

June 2020-current

Jan 2021-current

Wilkes University

Assisting multiple groups of students in learning Python, code management, and project management.

Work Study Supervisor

Jan 2020-current

Wilkes University

Assisted with inventory management, keeping track of rentals of video and audio equipment, and explained usage of equipment and software.

Awards



Dean's List

5 Semesters

Wilkes University

Recognized for work of high quality. Earned a GPA of 3.5 or higher in all courses taken.

Trustee's Scholarship

2017

Wilkes University

Awarded at admission for having a 4.0 High School GPA, and renewed each semester for maintaining a high GPA.



Adobe After Effects Clip Studio Paint HTML5 CSS/SCSS Unity Engine 2D animation



Logo Design Adobe Illustrator Adobe Dreamweaver Adobe Indesign Cinema 4D Python



Adobe Photoshop JavaScript Adobe Premiere Pro Communication Windows OS Front-End Web Dev



Costume Design Music Puzzle Games Cooking